Peter Agada

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

■ agadap46@gmail.com

**** +233 (0)20-195-3361

Pl/48 Lomotey Avenue, Spintex Accra

in linkedin.com/in/peter-adoyi-agada-771346187

github.com/theagester12345

peter-agada.com

I am a Experienced Full stack developer with a demonstrated history of working exclusively in the IT industry. Skilled in developing Android, web (frontend), backend, or a combination of all. Excellent problem solving, collaboration and communication skills.

SKILLS

- Frontend Technologies: HTML, CSS, Javascript, Bootstrap, React.js, Tailwind
- Backend Technologies: Java, Python, Spring, Jakarta EE, Django, CakePHP, Node.js, Express.js, Firebase
- Database Technologies: MySQL, Firebase/FireStore, MongoDB, Postgres
- Mobile Technologies: React Native, Android (with Java and Kotlin)
- Platform Technologies: Docker, Jenkins
- Misc: Version Control, CI/CD

EXPERIENCE

AUG 2022 - PRESENT

Cloud Native Java Engineer

Tech11 - Germany (Remote)

Responsibilities

- Contributed to the Development and Maintenace of Back End Modules
- Worked on cloud native applications using Jakarta EE, Docker and Jenkins
- · Collaborated with cross-functional teams to deliver high-quality software

FEB 2020 - JULY 2022

Full Stack Engineer

FirstLine24 Technology LTD, Ghana

Responsibilities

- Led the development of a consumer-to-consumer (C2C) e-commerce application using React.js for the front-end and Spring Boot, Express.js and Node.js for the back-end
- Contributed to the improvement of a Hospital Management System by fixing and adding new features to a CakePHP back-end and React.js front-end
- Collaborated with cross-functional teams to deliver high-quality software that met the needs of the target audience
- Mentored junior developers and participated in code reviews to ensure code quality
- · Wrote clean, testable, and maintainable code

Peter Agada

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

EXPERIENCE (CONTINUED)

SEP 2019 - AUG 2020

Full Stack Developer

ARSENETECH, Ghana

Responsibilities

- Led the development of an all-in-one mobility app for artisans, utilizing React Native for the front-end and Spring Boot for the back-end
- Collaborated with cross-functional teams to deliver a high-quality product that met the needs of the target audience
- Ensured code quality by writing clean, testable, and maintainable code and participating in code reviews

NOV 2017 - JUN 2019

Full Stack Developer

DIGIMASTERS, Ghana

Responsibilities

- · Responsible for developing and maintaining a revenue collection system
- Engineered a web portal using React.js
- · Built a back-end application using Spring Boot
- · Developed a mobile app using Native Android
- · Collaborated with cross-functional teams to deliver high-quality software
- · Wrote clean, testable, and maintainable code

JUN 2016 - SEP 2016

Intern

Ghana National Petroleum Company (GNPC), Ghana

JUN 2015 - SEP 2015

Intern

AgadaTech Solutions, Ghana

EDUCATION

SEP 2013 - MAY 2017

B.Sc. Computer Science

Kwame Nkrumah University of Science and Technology (KNUST) - Kumasi

SEP 2010 - APR 2013

WASSCE Certification - General Science

Presbyterian Boys' Senior High School - Legon

Peter Agada FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

PROJECTS

- LoopRx Web Service (Spring Boot, MySQL)
- Super2Odds (Android Java, Firebase)
- **Rev-Coms** (Android Java, Firebase)
- **DigiPay** (Android Java, Firebase)
- E-Recruit (HTML, CSS, Python, JavaScript, MySQL)
- AboboyaExpress (JavaScript, React Native, NodeJS, MySQL)